Guide to the Yale School of Drama Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Drama School, 1966-1983; Accession 1986-A-026
  - Correspondence (Dept, Theatre, School)
    - Television, 1980-1983 (Box 47, Folder 751)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1979-1981 (Box 47, Folder 752)
      - Manager's Bulletin, 1979-1981 (Box 47, Folder 753)
      - National Working Conference, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 754)
    - Theater Magazine, 1979-1981 (Box 48, Folder 755)
    - Tony Awards, 1979-1981 (Box 48, Folder 756)
    - Tuttle, Day, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 757)
    - U Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 759)
    - University of the State of New York: State Education Department, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 760)
    - U.S. Institute for Theatre Technology, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 761)
    - V Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 48, Folder 762)
    - W Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 48, Folder 763)
      - 1982 (Box 48, Folder 764)
      - 1983 (Box 48, Folder 765)
    - Wiggin and Dana, 1971-1972 (Box 48, Folder 766)
    - WGBH Boston: NEH Project, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 768)
    - Y Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 48, Folder 769)
    - Z Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 48, Folder 770)
    - Reading File (Correspondence):, 1979 June - September (Box 49, Folder 771)
      - 1979 Sep - Nov (Box 49, Folder 772)
      - 1979 Nov - 1980 Mar (Box 49, Folder 773)
      - 1980 Mar - Jun (Box 49, Folder 774)
      - 1980 Jul - Oct (Box 49, Folder 775)
      - 1980 Oct - 1981 Feb (Box 49, Folder 776)
      - 1981 Feb - Jul (Box 49, Folder 777)
  - Curricula and Courses
    - Acting Department, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 778)
      - Baker Salsbury and Directing, 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 779)
    - Acting/Directing, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 780)
    - About the Acting/Directing Program, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 781)
    - Acting: Drama School, 1979-1983 (Box 50, Folder 782)
    - Acting: Yale Repertory Theatre, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 783)
    - Memo to First- and Second-Year Acting Students, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 784)
    - Class Schedule: Drama School, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 785)
    - Curriculum and Registrar, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 786)
    - About the Design Program, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 787)
    - Design Department, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 788)
      - 1979-1983 (Box 50, Folder 789)
    - Directing, 1979-1983 (Box 50, Folder 790)
    - Doctor of Fine Arts Program, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 791)
    - Drama 1, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 792)
    - Drama 16, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 793)
    - Drama 36, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 794)
    - Drama 156, undated (Box 50, Folder 795)
    - Drama 176, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 796)
    - Artistic Director: Drama 321, 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 797)
    - Dramaturg's Guide, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 798)
    - Doctor of Fine Arts Program in Dramatic Literature and Criticism, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 799)
    - Dramaturgy and Criticism, 1980-1983 (Box 51, Folder 800)
    - Internships, 1979-1981 (Box 51, Folder 801)
    - Internships, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 802)
    - Open Dates/Special Events, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 803)
    - Playwriting, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 804)
      - 1979-1983 (Box 51, Folder 805)
    - Summer Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 806)
    - Summer Pre-College Program in Acting, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 807)
    - Technical Department, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 808)
    - Technical, Design and Production Department, 1980-1983 (Box 51, Folder 809)
    - Theatre Administration Assignments, 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 810)
    - Theatre Administration Courses, 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 811)
    - About the Theatre Administration Program, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 812)
    - Theatre Administration Program
      - 1969-1971 (Box 51, Folder 813)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 814)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 815)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 816)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 52, Folder 817)
      - 1977 (Box 52, Folder 818)
      - 1978 (Box 52, Folder 819)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 820)
      - 1979 (Box 52, Folder 821)
      - 1980 (Box 52, Folder 822)
      - 1981 (Box 53, Folder 823)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 824)
      - 1982 (Box 53, Folder 825)
      - 1983 (Box 53, Folder 826)
    - Theatre Administration Program: Members, Evaluations, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 827)
    - Job Opportunities for Theatre Administrators, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 828)
    - Director Thesis Projects, 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 829)
    - Thesis Proposal (Romito), 1979 (Box 53, Folder 832)
    - Yale School of Drama Course Listings, 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 836)
  - Dean's Office/Faculty Memos
    - Admissions, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 837)
    - Annual Report
      - 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 838)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 839)
    - Brochure, 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 840)
    - Brustein, Robert, 1971-1979 (Box 54, Folder 841)
    - Campus Police, 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 842)
    - "Centerline" Newsletter, 1975-1978 (Box 54, Folder 843)
    - Commencement, 1967-1969 (Box 54, Folder 844)
    - Computer Matters, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 845)
    - Course Evaluations: Acting Department, undated (Box 54, Folder 846)
      - Theatre Administration Department, 1981 Spring (Box 54, Folder 847)
        - 1981 Fall (Box 54, Folder 848)
        - 1982 (Box 54, Folder 849)
    - Directory: Addresses, Telephone Numbers, Notes (Students), 1977-1980 (Box 55, Folder 850)
      - Faculty, Student, Staff, 1977-1979 (Box 55, Folder 851)
    - Electro-Mechanical Lab, undated (Box 55, Folder 852)
    - Faculty, 1977-1978 (Box 55, Folder 853)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1968-1971 (Box 55, Folder 854)
      - Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 855)
        - 1977-1983 (Box 55, Folder 856)
    - Faculty: Memoranda, 1977-1980 (Box 55, Folder 857)
    - Financial Aid, 1979-1983 (Box 55, Folder 858)
    - Financial Management Information System (Report), 1980 (Box 55, Folder 859)
    - Gister, Earl (Associate Dean), 1979-1983 (Box 55, Folder 860)
    - Housing, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 861)
    - Materials Gathered for the History of the Drama School, 1972-1973 (Box 55, Folder 862)
    - Parking, 1967-1980 (Box 55, Folder 863)
    - Placement, 1977-1981 (Box 55, Folder 865)
    - Press Releases and Publicity: Drama School
      - 1968-1969 (Box 55, Folder 866)
      - 1970 (Box 55, Folder 867)
      - 1979 (Box 55, Folder 868)
      - 1980-1982 (Box 56, Folder 869)
    - Program Advisory Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 870)
    - "The Prompter" (Newsletter), 1979-1983 (Box 56, Folder 871)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 872)
    - Registrar: Drama School
      - 1979-1980 (Box 56, Folder 873)
      - 1981 (Box 56, Folder 874)
      - 1982 (Box 56, Folder 875)
      - 1983 (Box 56, Folder 876)
    - Richards, Lloyd (Dean), 1978-1981 (Box 56, Folder 877)
    - Safety (Job), 1970-1972 (Box 56, Folder 878)
    - School Car Sign-Out Sheet, undated (Box 56, Folder 879)
    - Security, 1979-1981 (Box 56, Folder 880)
    - Social Events, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 881)
    - Speaking Engagements, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 882)
    - Staff: Drama School, 1977-1979 (Box 56, Folder 883)
    - Staff Meetings (Minutes)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 56, Folder 884)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 885)
    - Student Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 56, Folder 886)
    - "The Web" Newsletter, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 887)
    - Miscellaneous Memos and Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 56, Folder 888)
      - 1979 (Box 56, Folder 889)
      - 1980-1982 (Box 56, Folder 890)
    - American Repertory Theatre: Confidential Memo, 1980 (Box 56a, Folder 891)
  - Alumni
    - Alumni Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 893)
      - Placement, Requests for Transcripts
        - 1970-1975 (Box 57, Folder 894)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 57, Folder 895)
        - 1980-1982 (Box 57, Folder 896)
    - Alumni Lists: Chauncey, Samuel (Yale University Secretary), 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 897)
    - Alumni Matters, 1972-1975 (Box 57, Folder 898)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 899)
    - Alumni Records Office, 1979-1982 (Box 57, Folder 900)
    - Alumni Vocational Questionnaire, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 901)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 902)
      - Committee on the Arts, 1976-1980 (Box 57, Folder 903)
    - Class of 1931 Day, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 904)
    - Class of 1940 Day, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 905)
    - Contributions, 1978-1979 (Box 57, Folder 906)
    - Drama Alumni Association: Activities, 1968-1973 (Box 57, Folder 907)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 57, Folder 908)
      - Directory of Drama Alumni, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 909)
      - Drama School 50th Anniversary, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 910)
      - Executive Committee, 1968-1980 (Box 58, Folder 911 - 912)
      - Faculty, 1974-1976 (Box 58, Folder 913)
    - Drama Alumni Bibliography, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 914)
    - Drama Alumni Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 915)
    - Drama Alumni Newsletter, 1968-1976 (Box 58, Folder 916)
      - 1977-1982 (Box 58, Folder 917)
    - Drama School: Alumni Relations, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 918)
    - Employment Status of Former Y.S.D. Students in Theatre Administration, 1975-1977 (Box 58, Folder 919)
    - Gifts and Grants Procedures, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 921)
    - Grants, 1971-1973 (Box 58, Folder 922)
    - National Endowment for the Arts: Internship, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 925)
    - Oenslager Collection, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 926)
    - Special Gifts, 1963-1972 (Box 59, Folder 927)
    - Yale Alumni Association, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 929)
    - Yale Alumni Fund: Status Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 59, Folder 930)
    - Yale Club of New York City, 1979-1982 (Box 59, Folder 931)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre: Alumni (Box 59, Folder 932)
    - Yale University Office of Development and Alumni Affairs, 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 933)
    - Yale University: Director, Grant and Contract Administration, 1981-1983 (Box 59, Folder 934)
  - Plays and Productions
    - Actors' Equity, 1977-1978 (Box 60, Folder 935)
    - "The Alchemist": Production Staff, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 936)
    - Annex, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 937)
    - "Are You Now or Have You Ever Been?": Production Staff, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 938)
    - Audience Development Director, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 939)
    - Audition Tour, 1977-1978 (Box 60, Folder 940)
    - "Baal": Production Staff, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 941)
    - Jean-Louis Barrault: Press Release, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 942)
    - "The Bewitched", 1982 (Box 60, Folder 943)
    - Black Workshop, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 944)
    - Yale Cabaret, 1979-1982 (Box 60, Folder 945)
    - Calendar Listings, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 946)
    - Children's Theatre, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 947)
    - "In the Clap Shack": Production Staff, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 948)
    - "Cock-A-Doodle Dandy'', 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 949)
    - Complimentary Tickets, 1971-1982 (Box 60, Folder 950)
    - Costume Storage, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 951)
    - "Deadwood": Production Staff, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 952)
    - Design, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 953)
    - Drama Productions, Inc., 1973-1977 (Box 60, Folder 954)
    - Drama School Productions, 1977-1978 (Box 60, Folder 955)
    - Dramat, 1977-1978 (Box 60, Folder 956)
      - 1980 (Box 60, Folder 957)
    - "Edward II", 1973 (Box 60, Folder 958)
    - "Empire Builders", 1970 (Box 60, Folder 959)
    - The Ensemble Company, 1977-1978 (Box 60, Folder 960)
      - 1979-1982 (Box 60, Folder 961)
    - Fire Department, 1969-1971 (Box 60, Folder 962)
    - "Good", 1982 (Box 60, Folder 963)
    - "Inheritors": General Information, undated (Box 60, Folder 964)
    - "Julius Caesar", 1969 (Box 60, Folder 966)
    - "King Learn": Production Staff, undated (Box 60, Folder 967)
    - Jerzy Kozinski Press Release, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 968)
    - Labor Standards, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 969)
    - "La Turista", 1970 (Box 60, Folder 970)
    - "The Living Theatr": Reviews, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 971)
    - "The Lower Depths": Production Staff, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 972)
    - "Macbett": Production Staff, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 973)
    - "Mad Dog Blues": Production Staff, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 974)
    - "Mad Dog Blues", 1975 (Box 61, Folder 975)
    - "Major Barbara", 1973 (Box 61, Folder 976)
    - Media Production Unit, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 977)
    - "The Mirror": Production Staff, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 978)
    - Moliere, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 979)
    - The Negro Ensemble, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 980)
    - "1913": Production Staff, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 981)
    - Oxford and Cambridge Shakespeare Company, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 982)
    - "The Physicists", 1970 (Box 61, Folder 983)
    - "Pillars of Society", 1982 (Box 61, Folder 984)
    - "The Poor of New York", 1970 (Box 61, Folder 985)
    - Production Schedules, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 986)
      - 1979-1982 (Box 61, Folder 987)
    - Productions: Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 61, Folder 988)
    - Program Samples, 1968-1970 (Box 61, Folder 989)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 990)
    - "The Royal Pardon", 1972-1973 (Box 61, Folder 991)
    - Reviews, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 992)
    - Reviews: Yale Daily News, 1968-1969 (Box 61, Folder 993)
    - Safety, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 994)
    - Scripts, Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 61, Folder 995)
    - Season, 1976-1977 (Box 61, Folder 996)
    - Sound Equipment, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 997)
    - Special Scripts, 1977-1978 (Box 61, Folder 998)
    - Sunday Series, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 999)
    - "Sweeney Agonistes"/"Hughie", 1969 (Box 61, Folder 1000)
    - Technical Department, 1971-1972, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 1001)
    - Touring Companies, 1977-1980 (Box 62, Folder 1002)
      - 1981 (Box 62, Folder 1003)
    - "Welcome to the Funeral of One of Us", 1969 (Box 62, Folder 1004)
    - "Women Beware Women": Production Staff, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 1005)
  - MEMOSANDADMINISTRATION
    - Affirmative Action, 1977-1982 (Box 63, Folder 1006)
    - Afro-American Center and Studies, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 1007)
    - Afro-American Faculty Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 1008)
    - Afro-American Studies, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 1009)
    - Arts Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 63, Folder 1010)
    - Yale Cabaret, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 1011)
    - Campaign for Yale, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 1012)
    - Campus Police, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 1013)
    - Yale University: Office of the Bursar, 1980-1983 (Box 63, Folder 1014)
      - Office of President's Committee on Non-Traditional Education, 1981-1983 (Box 63, Folder 1015)
      - President's Committee on Racial and Ethnic Harassment, 1981-1983 (Box 63, Folder 1016)
    - Committee on Special Programs in the Arts, 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 1017)
    - Yale University Comptroller: Advisory Group on Financial Accounting, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 1018)
    - Correspondence: Faculty Appointments and Procedure, 1977-1982 (Box 63, Folder 1019)
    - Yale University: Finance and Administration, 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 1020)
    - Financial Aid, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 1021)
    - Yale University: General Counsel and Director of Government Relations, 1980-1983 (Box 64, Folder 1022)
    - Graduate and Professional Assembly, 1980-1983 (Box 64, Folder 1023)
    - Graduate School: Council on Priorities and Planning, 1972-1973 (Box 64, Folder 1024)
      - 1964-1973 (Box 64, Folder 1025)
    - Graduate Financial Aid, 1969-1973 (Box 64, Folder 1026)
    - Honorary Degrees Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 64, Folder 1027)
    - Housing, 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 1028)
    - Institute for Social and Policy Studies: Mass Communication Seminar, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 1029 - 1030)
    - Yale University Library: Copyright Compliance, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 1031)
    - Eugene O'Neill Library Collection, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 1032)
    - Machine Contracts and Manuals, 1980-1981 (Box 65, Folder 1033)
    - Yale University News Releases, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 1034)
    - Office of Institutional Research, 1971-1972 (Box 65, Folder 1035)
      - 1979-1983 (Box 65, Folder 1036)
    - Yale University: Personnel Department, 1980-1983 (Box 65, Folder 1037)
    - Personnel: Appointments, 1973-1975 (Box 65, Folder 1038)
      - Memos on Employment, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 1039)
    - Office of the President, 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 1040)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 65, Folder 1041)
      - Evaluations of Managerial and Professional Staff, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 1042)
    - Yale University Press, 1981-1983 (Box 65, Folder 1043)
    - Yale University: Office of the Provost, 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 1044)
    - rehabilitation Act and Handicapped Access, 1976-1979 (Box 65, Folder 1049)
    - Safety Violations, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 1050)
    - School of Art, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 1051)
    - School of Music, 1979-1982 (Box 65, Folder 1052)
    - School of Organization and Management, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 1053)
    - Office of the Secretary, 1982 (Box 65, Folder 1054)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 65, Folder 1055)
      - Honorary Degree Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 66, Folder 1056)
    - Security, 1980-1982 (Box 66, Folder 1057)
    - Shuttle Bus, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 1058)
    - Strike, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 1059)
    - Union Drive, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 1060)
    - University Council: Drama School Reports, 1973-1980 (Box 66, Folder 1061)
    - Yale University: United Way, 1979-1981 (Box 66, Folder 1062)
      - Office of the Vice-president for Finance and Administration, 1979-1983 (Box 66, Folder 1063)
    - Yale Center for British Art, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 1064)
    - Yale College: All Colleges Excepting Morse, 1982-1983 (Box 66, Folder 1065)
      - Morse College (Box 66, Folder 1066)
      - Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 1067)
      - Office of the Dean, 1981-1982 (Box 66, Folder 1068)
      - Dean's Advisory Committee: Members, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 1069)
      - Theatre Studies Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 66, Folder 1070)
      - Undergraduate Departments, 1979-1983 (Box 66, Folder 1071)
    - Yale Dramat, 1980-1983 (Box 66, Folder 1072)
    - Yale University: Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 66, Folder 1073)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 1074)
        - 1982-1983 (Box 67, Folder 1075)
    - University Matters, 1979-1981 (Box 67, Folder 1076)
    - Student Evaluations and Theatre Administration Program, 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 1079)
    - Admissions, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 1080)
    - Baker, Sidney, 1980-1983 (Box 68, Folder 1081)
    - Graduate School: Council on Priorities and Planning, 1980-1983 (Box 68, Folder 1082)
    - Technical Design and Production Department, 1981-1983 (Box 68, Folder 1083)
    - Dramaturgy and Criticism Program, 1979-1983 (Box 68, Folder 1084)
    - Theatre Administration: Student Records, 1977-1980 (Box 68, Folder 1085)
    - Students: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 1086)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 1087)
- Records, 1975-1989; Accession 1990-A-032
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2024
  - A, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 3)
  - Accuracy in Media, Inc., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Actors Equity Association, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Actors Equity Association, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Actors Equity: Non-traditional Casting, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AIDS Benefit, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Music Theatre Festival, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Playhouse, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Shakespeare Theatre, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Shakespeare Theatre Task Force, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - American Theatre Association: Black Theatre Project, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Theatre, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Theatre Wing, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Applications for Assistants, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Arts Council of Greater New Haven, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Aspen Institute: Film Series Steering Committee, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Atkinson Memorial Committee, Brooks, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Atlanta Center for the Arts, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Andelco, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - B, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 22 - 25)
  - Baldwin, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Berkeley Repertory Theatre, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Beverly Hills National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Black Masks, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Black Theatre Newsletter, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bushfire Theatre, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - C, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 34 - 37)
  - Cachiero Productions, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Center for Study of Filmed History, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Christian Science Monitor, Rushworth Kidder, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Columbia: Paul Robeson Scholarship Fund, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Commonwealth Awards, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 42 - 43)
  - Connecticut Arts Awards, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Connecticut College Commencement, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts
    - 1985 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - 1986 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - 1987 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - 1988 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Connecticut Originals WFSB - Ch. 3, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - D, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 54 - 55)
  - Daishiki Project Theatre, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Dramatists Guild, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Development (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Director -- Ann Johnson, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - ABC, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - "Arts at Yale" (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Arts Awards, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Audrey Wood Scholarship, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Boston Project, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - California Alumni -- President Dinner, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - California, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - California Trip, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - California, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Johnny Carson, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Columbia Pictures-Vincent, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Drama Alumni Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Yale 60th Anniversary, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Candidates Development, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Development Director, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Individual Contribution Solicitation Campaign (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Corporate Mail, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Equitable, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Lloyd Richards: Exxon Luncheon Materials, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Exxon, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Home Box Office, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - International Business Machines, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Molly Kazan Award, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Klavsen Scholarship, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - General Electric Corporation Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Maine Property, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Miller and Company, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - National Broadcasting Companies, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Priority Shopping List, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - National Endowment for the Arts
    - Professional Theatre Training Grant, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Theatre Magazine Grant, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Theatre Program Director: Ed Martenson, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Newagon Inn, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Oenslager, 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 105 - 106)
  - Phillip Morris and Proctor and Gamble, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Rep Patrons Program, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Proposals (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Rockefeller, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Rockefeller: Joanna Glass Residence, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - San Francisco, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Talia Shire Party, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Schubert Organization, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Special Events, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Wright, 1983, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 118)